<root>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Klingon multitasking systems do not support 'time-sharing'. When a Klingon program wants to run, it challenges the scheduler in hand-to-hand combat and owns the machine.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Defensive programming? Never! Klingon programs are always on the offense. Yes, offensive programming is what we do best.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Specifications are for the weak and timid!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[This machine is GAGH! I need quad CORE processors if I am to do battle with this code!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[You cannot really appreciate Dilbert unless you've read it in the original Klingon.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Indentation?! - I will show you how to indent when I indent your skull!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[What is this talk of 'release'? Klingons do not make software 'releases'. Our software 'escapes' leaving a bloody trail of designers and quality assurance people in its wake.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Klingon function calls do not have 'parameters' - they have 'arguments' -- and they ALWAYS WIN THEM.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Debugging? Klingons do not debug. Our software does not coddle the weak. Bugs are good for building character in the user.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[I have challenged the entire ISO-9000 quality assurance team to a Bat-Leth contest on the holodeck. They will not concern us again.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[A TRUE Klingon Warrior does not comment his code!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[By filing this bug report you have challenged the honor of my family. Prepare to die!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[You question the worthiness of my code? I should kill you where you stand!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Our users will know fear and cower before our software! Ship it! Ship it and let them flee like the dogs they are!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Our competitors are without honor!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Python? That is for children. A Klingon Warrior uses only machine code, keyed in on the front panel switches in raw binary.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA["Klingon programs don't do accountancy. For that, you need a Ferengi.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Klingon multitasking systems do not support 'time-sharing'. When a Klingon program wants to run, it challenges the scheduler in hand-to-hand combat and owns the machine.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Perhaps it IS a good day to die! I say we ship it!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[My program has just dumped Stova Core!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Behold, the keyboard of Kalis! The greatest Klingon code warrior that ever lived!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[This code is a piece of crap! You have no honor!]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[C++? That is for children. A Klingon Warrior uses only machine code, keyed in on the front panel switches in raw binary.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[You humans call this thing a 'cursor' and you move it with 'mouse'! Bah! A Klingon would not use such a device. We have a Karaghht-Gnot - which is best translated as "An Aiming Daggar of 16x16 pixels" and we move it using a Gshnarrrf which is a creature from the Klingon homeworld which posesses just one, (disproportionately large) testicle...which it rubs along the ground.....uh do we really need to talk about this?]]></klingon>
  <klingon>
    <![CDATA[I am without honor...my children are without honor... My father coded at the Battle of Kittimer...and...and...he...
      HE ALLOWED HIMSELF TO BE MICROMANAGED.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Microsoft is actually a secret Farengi-Klingon alliance designed to cripple the Federation. The Farengi are doing the marketing and the Klingons are writing the code.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Specifications are for the weak and timid.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[State-of-the-art hardware is a prerequisite to do battle with code.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[One cannot truly appreciate "Dilbert" without reading it in the original Klingon.]]></klingon>
  <klingon><![CDATA[Quality Assurance issues are best solved with a Batleth.]]></klingon>
</root>
